{
  "id": 801,
  "themeId": 8,
  "name": "Writing and Reading ça va Test 1",
  "description": "Autogenerated quiz",
  "version": "2.2.1",
  "lastUpdated": "13/04/2025",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you say “how are you”? (informal)",
      "options": [
        "Ça va ?",
        "Ça te va ?",
        "Ça vous va ?",
        "Ça le va ?"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Ça va ?",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"excuse-me\"? (formal)",
      "options": [
        "Excusez-me",
        "Excusez-moi",
        "Excuse-moi",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Excusez-moi",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “how are you”? (formal)",
      "options": [
        "Comment allez-vous ?",
        "Comment vas-tu ?",
        "Comment allez-votre ?",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Comment allez-vous ?",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “my name is”? (informal)",
      "options": [
        "Je m’appelle",
        "Moi, c’est",
        "Mon prénom, c’est",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “I’m American”? (feminine)",
      "options": [
        "Je suis américain.",
        "Je suis amèricane.",
        "Je suis Américaine.",
        "Je suis américaine."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Je suis américaine.",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “I’m doing well”?",
      "options": [
        "Ça va.",
        "Ça va pas bien.",
        "Je vais bien.",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"nice to meet you\"? (informal)",
      "options": [
        "Sympa de vous rencontrer",
        "C’était bien de te rencontrer",
        "C’était sympa de te rencontrer.",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "C’était sympa de te rencontrer.",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"I’m practising my French\"?(informal)",
      "options": [
        "Je pratique mon français.",
        "Je m’entraîne à parler français.",
        "Je m’exerce à parler français.",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you gesture \"hello\"? (informal and casual)",
      "options": [
        "Hug the personne",
        "Kiss on the cheeks",
        "Shake hands",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kiss on the cheeks",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"I miss my family\"?",
      "options": [
        "Ma famille te manque.",
        "Ma famille me manque.",
        "Ma famille moi manque.",
        "Je manque ma famille."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Ma famille me manque.",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}